

hellotushaar@gmail.com Bengaluru, India

linkedin.com/in/hellotushaar

Experiences

Front-End Developer, UI / UX Designer · 3rd Eye Visions

July 2022 - October 2022

As an intern at 3rd Eye Visions, my role was to design user interface and user experience solutions for a variety of digital products. I was also responsible for the development of several web applications. Other roles and responsibilities include:

- To design and develop unique digital products.
- To maintain the products.
- · To collaborate with team members to build killer solutions.

Front-end Developer, Technical Support · Vibable Media

August 2019 - September 2020

Vibable Media is a digital marketing startup agency based in Dhaka, Bangladesh. My role was to create the agency's official website to showcase its services, accomplishment, and agenda to its potential customers. Other functions and responsibilities include:

- Maintain the digital platforms and assets of the agency.
- Develop and deliver high-performing digital products.
- Assist non-technical members and employees in their tasks.

Licenses & Certifications

(ISC)² Certified in Cybersecurity (CC)

December 2022 - (ISC)²

The CC provides in-depth knowledge necessary to protect against cyber threats and secure systems and networks effectively. The comprehensive course and exam structure help to achieve an unshakable foundation in cybersecurity concepts, tools, and best practices needed by a cybersecurity professional in any organization.

Microsoft Certified: Security, Compliance and Identity Fundamentals (SC-900)

January 2023 - Microsoft

The Microsoft Certified: Security, Compliance and Identity Fundamentals (SC-900) certification validates foundational knowledge of security, compliance, and identity concepts, core services, and core security technologies in Microsoft Azure. The hands-on lab experience helped to validate the ability to implement security, compliance, and identity solutions in Microsoft Azure.

Introduction

Tushar is a self-taught tech enthusiast with diverse skills in web development, UI/UX design and testing, programming, social media marketing, and an invulnerable desire to improve continuously. He is intensely interested in and dedicated to cybersecurity and cloud computing. In the near future, he sees himself as an ethical hacker, committing himself to ensure digital safety and security for billions. He is always working on expanding his knowledge and improving his skills, making him a qualified asset to the industry.

Expertise

Frontend Development.

UI / UX Design & Testing.

Python Programming.

Microsoft Azure.

Red Teaming.

Identity & Access Management.

Web App Penetration Testing.

Technologies

Python, Javascript, VCS, Kali Linux, Burp Suite, Nmap, Azure Active Directory, Google Workspace.

Community Activities

CodeX Club · GITAM University

August 2022 - Backend Lead & Technical Support

CodeX is a student-run club for coding and all things technology at GITAM University. As a core member of the club, I am responsible for holding events to help club members develop their web development skills. I am also responsible for handling projects related to the club.

CySec Club · GITAM University

August 2022 - Member

CySec is a club that aims to help the students of GITAM University to learn about cybersecurity and to help to develop their skills in cybersecurity. As a member of the club,

- I build home labs to implement offensive security.
- · I learn with others about new tools and technologies.
- I collaborate with other members to help each other get better.

Education

Graduation · Bachelor's of Computer Applications

2021 to 2024 · Gandhi Institute of Technology and Management, Bengaluru, India

As a student of BCA, I am learning computer science and software fundamentals from some of the most gifted and supportive professors at GITAM University. The program curriculum includes programming languages (Python, C++, Javascript, Java, R, PHP), information technology, data analysis, operating systems fundamentals, web technologies, data structures, data communication and networking, Unix programming, and many more. Additionally,

- I received the SII scholarship to pursue my undergraduate degree in India.
- Besides the core subjects mentioned above, I am encouraged to learn and engage with soft skills, club activities, venture development, sports, and many more.

Higher Secondary School · Science

Bangladesh Air Force Shaheen College, Chittagong, Bangladesh

Studied science subjects including Information Technology, Physics, Mathematics, Biology, and Chemistry.

Languages

English (Expert)

Bangla (Native)

Hindi (Conversational)

Spanish (Written)

Hobbies

Traveling, Blogging, Web Research.

Contact Information

Email: hellotushaar@gmail.com Website: www.hellotushaar.me

Linkedln: www.linkedin.com/in/hellotushaar GitHub: www.qithub.com/hellotushaar